Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Let's go
This world's a riot of color
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
Use your heart and look with care
Find the truth right beside you
Hey you could or better
Truth and lies
Can't escape the heart's gray smoke
Take all your courage
Maybe then you can save the world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
For your spine
Miasma Castle
Locky, please help me!
Miss, do you think I can still help?
It's dirty. Oh no!
Good
All wiped clean
Jingjing, run!
If I weren't so quick
we'd have been...
Hello? Detective Chen
I've heard so much about you
I'd like to ask you to help me find
a sixteen-year-old miracle doctor
A miracle doctor?
I'm sorry
I won't take this case
Fine, don't take it
Your little nephew is now in my hands
If you insist on not showing up, huh?
Uncle!
Locky!
We're fine
Don't worry
Ah, Uncle
Uncle, you're so lame!
Coming to a fancy villa banquet
dressed like that?
Huh? How did you get here too?
Some people are just low-class
Nothing's as elegant as me.
Welcome, everyone.
I'm the master here.
Goldsworth.
What a terrible name!
Poison Castle. Poison Castle.
Who are you, really?
Show yourself, now.
I invited you all here to ask you to find a doctor for me.
So you're looking for a doctor.
That's easy.
I can send my former men to find him for you.
There, there, off you go.
I'm sure you've all heard of
Miracle Doctor Yunfeng, right?
Locky, let's go.
Great detective.
Did you think my Golden Poison Castle was just a scary name?
The reason I don't show myself
is because the whole hall is already filled with the poison flowers on the tables
and the toxins they give off.
You're already poisoned.
In this world,
Only Miracle Doctor Yunfeng can give you the antidote.
I hope you find him soon.
Good luck, everyone.
Uncle——
The poison's acting up.
Looks like I'm done for.
Buy me a Magic Horn Detective toy.
Uncle, wait for me!
Locky, wait for me!
Are you sure these kids who look like they're not too bright
will really find Yunfeng?
Don't worry. Just wait for them to bring back that miracle doctor.
And to think I treated him well back then.
But he stole the Colitas flower seeds
I used to make banned drugs.
But...
Why exactly are you helping me find Yunfeng?
For Love!
For Ideals!
Uncle, it looks like nobody's lived here for a long time.
Uncle, this place is a real mess.
Detective Chen.
I checked Yunfeng's records.
So many awards!
The once world-famous miracle doctor Yunfeng
was ruined by helping Goldsworth Pharmaceuticals
develop those banned drugs.
And in the end, the government revoked his medical license.
Not long after that,
Yunfeng suddenly and mysteriously disappeared.
Oh? Hmm...
Huh? Uncle's in this photo!
Huh?
The one on the far left must be Miracle Doctor Yunfeng.
But Uncle, how come you're in the photo too?
This time Goldsworth is looking for Yunfeng,
probably to develop new banned drugs again.
We have to find Yunfeng before Goldsworth does.
So, Detective Jimmy,
please, you must tell me all the intel you have.
Tell us! Tell us! Tell us!
Tell me, tell me! Come on, Uncle!
Fine, fine! I really can't hide anything from you guys.
Yunfeng is a friend I grew up with.
Later I became a detective,
while he inherited his father's clinic.
Then who's that pretty lady next to him?
Her name is Su Wu.
[Ending Theme]
All alone, lonely and forlorn,
At times like this in life,
There's bound to be some unhappiness.
Saying goodbye to today
Always leaves you feeling lost
Look at tomorrow
Waving to me from your horizon
Every day is just the sun rising and setting
Turning into time, dreaming more and more
Expecting every second and moment in life
Bright eyes are twinkling
Smiles that face the sun
Trampling the bridge at the dim intersection
Isn't that so
Aunt Su Wu
Little one
Do you know him?